<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installation on iter8 Documentation</title>
    <link>/introduction/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installation on iter8 Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/introduction/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Iter8 on Kubernetes and Istio</title>
      <link>/introduction/installation/kubernetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction/installation/kubernetes/</guid>
      <description>These instructions show you how to set up iter8 on Kubernetes with Istio.
Prerequisites  Kubernetes v1.11 or newer. Istio v1.1.5 and newer. Your Istio installation must have at least the istio-pilot as well as telemetry and Prometheus enabled.  Install iter8 on Kubernetes iter8 has two components, iter8_analytics and iter8_controller. To install them, follow the instructions below. For additional considerations when installing iter8 on Red Hat OpenShift, check out these instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iter8 on Red Hat OpenShift</title>
      <link>/introduction/installation/red-hat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction/installation/red-hat/</guid>
      <description>These instructions show you how to set up iter8 on Red Hat OpenShift.
Prerequisites We recommend using the Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh. This can be installed using the Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh Operator. For details, see: https://docs.openshift.com/container-platform/4.3/service_mesh/service_mesh_install/installing-ossm.html.
Installing the Service Mesh involves installing the Elasticsearch, Jaeger, Kiali and Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh Operators, creating and managing a ServiceMeshControlPlane resource to deploy the control plane, and creating a ServiceMeshMemberRoll resource to specify the namespaces associated with the Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>